准备好了吗  孩子们
Are you ready, kids?
好了船长
Aye aye, captain
我听不见
I can't hear you
好了船长
Aye aye, captain
是谁住在深海的大菠萝里
Who lives in a pineapple under the sea?
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
方方黄黄伸缩自如
Absorbent and yellow and porous is he
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
如果四处探险是你的愿望
If nautical nonsense be something you wish
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
那就敲敲甲板让大鱼开路
Then drop on the deck and flop like a fish
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
准备
Ready
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
小个子队长
编剧
分镜总监
翻译: 1440kHz
指导总监
动画总监
统筹
联合监制
监制
本字幕仅限学习交流
严禁用于商业用途
要来了
Incoming
蟹堡王
痞老板  你可真是个大麻烦
Plankton, you're a hot mess
偷我秘方偷那么多次  全是你活该
Serves ya right fer tryin' to steal me formular
for the gazillionth time
我会复仇的
I'll have my revenge
给我记住
Mark my words
真是的
Come on
还没结束呢
This isn't over
忙活一天累坏了是吗
Hard day at work?
我知道你需要什么
I know what you need
凯伦  我偷不到蟹黄堡的秘密配方
Oh, Karen, I'm never gonna get that Krabby Patty formula
味道不错
Not bad
祝你掉脸皮快乐
Enjoy your molten face peels
我的海滩烧烤啊
Holy clambake
美人鱼战士和企鹅男孩
Are Mermaid Man and Barnacle Boy
难道就要被射线恶魔和邪恶帮同伙
about to become hero flambé cooked by Man Ray
烧成烤肉了吗
and his criminal posse of E.V.I.L.?
给我烤
I hope so
我就爱看坏蛋占优势
I love it when the villains gain the upper hand
我们的英雄面临危机
As our heroes face certain doom
同时坏蛋们逃往地下秘密基地去了
the villains escape to their secret underground lair
那当然了
Of course
我只要加入邪恶帮就行了
All I need to do is join the criminals of E.V.I.L.
他们可以帮我打败老螃蟹
They'll help me defeat Krabs
好办法
Smart thinking
你可以当  毛巾侠
You can go as "Towel Man"
少自作聪明
Don't be a wisenheimer
我才不披这破布
I can't accessorize this old rag
我要真衣服
I need a real costume
斗篷还是得改短点
Maybe a shorter cape
这里一定就是他们秘密基地入口
This must be the entrance to their secret lair
潜进垃圾箱里就能进去了
A little dumpster dive, and I'm in
门在哪
Where's the door?
邪恶帮基地
在这
找错垃圾箱了
Wrong dumpster
果然
Of course
秘密基地
在吗
Hello?
邪恶帮                   继续走                      往这边
我是来加入邪恶帮的
I'm here to join the forces of E.V.I.L.
舞台大门
兄弟
Dude
什么
Wha--
登记完好好等
Sign in and wait your turn
红皮革  黄皮革
Red leather, yellow leather
所有人给我下车
Get out of the car, fellas
把钱都交出来  放进袋子里
Take all your money and put it in the bag
错  海绵宝宝先生
No, Mr. Bob
我要炸了你们
I expect you to fry
等到满月升起
When the full moon rises
我是复仇者
I am the Strangler
I'm the Strangler
这黄色的是什么东西
What is this yellow thing?
某种霉菌吗
Some kind of mold?
生存还是
To be or--
提词
line
来的这一大票流氓挺出色  对不对
We've got
quite an impressive rogues gallery up there, eh?
感谢你们从见不得人的日程中抽空
Thank you for taking time
out of your scandalous schedules
来邪恶帮面试
to try out for E.V.I.L.
众所周知
As you all know
邪恶帮新人选只有一个
we can only pick one new villain to join Team E.V.I.L.
那就开始面试吧
so let the judging begin
点到谁就选谁
Eeny, meeny, miney--
诺斯费拉图
Nosferatu
不行  射线恶魔
No way, Man Ray
我才最先
I was first
最先走人
First to go bye-bye
消失
Be gone
诺斯费拉图  继续
Nosferatu, proceed
哑剧
Mime?
他邪恶超能力就是演哑剧
Mime is his evil power?
螳螂机器人
Robot Mantis
哒哒
Ta-da
你大胆
How dare you
钢琴好不容易才调好音
We just had that piano tuned
点到谁就选谁
Eeny, meeny, miney--
谢尔顿痞老板
Sheldon J. Plankton?
谢了  女士
Thanks, ma'am
不过
but, uh
配乐就用不着了
music won't be necessary
对
Right
请问你的坏蛋超能力是什么  小家伙
So what's your supervillain power, little guy?
我敢说这超能力是我的邪恶大智慧
Well, I'd venture to say
it would be my massive, evil intellect
出彩
Impressive
那你对你未来五年的方向有何愿景
So where do you see yourself in the next five years?
一旦我最终得到了秘密配方
Well, once I finally have the secret formula
最终导致的末世后的全球毁灭帝国
The post-apocalyptic global empire
of destruction that results
就将会是我的
will be mine
而我将风风光光坐在你们的尸骨堆上
and I'll be sitting pretty on a pile of your bones
一听就有反派本色
That sounds pretty villainous
好  你可以进入测试阶段
Okay, you'll move on to the test phase
但首先得先取个像样的坏蛋名
But first, you'll need a proper supervillain name
要不要  绿豆先生
How about "Mr. Green Bean"?
小咪咪的绿绿人
The "Itsy Bitsy Green Guy"
不行  太长了
No, too long
要不然就  小个子队长
How about "Captain Pipsqueak"?
好
Yeah
我喜欢
I love it
这样就行了
That settles it
小个子队长
Captain Pipsqueak
之后应该会再调整吧
We can tweak that later, right?
好了  全体成员
Okay, team
测试小个子队长真实世界中的恶行吧
let's test Captain Pipsqueak's villainy
in the real world
婴儿宝宝乐园
第一项测试是给我们买午饭
Your first test is to get us lunch
去儿童乐园买个25磅的全家桶
a 25-pound bucket from Weenie Hut Jr.
加邪恶酱
With Evil sauce
多加邪恶酱
Extra Evil sauce
这恶行挺怪  不过没问题
Odd caper, but no problemo
我要来份25磅儿童热狗全家桶
I need a 25-pound Weenie bucket, please
做好点
and make it snappy
多加邪恶酱
And extra Evil sauce
这单我认得
I know that order
你是邪恶帮成员
You're one of those E.V.I.L. guys
你们一律禁止入内
You're all banned
绝不为邪恶帮提供食品
快把餐给我
Just give me my order
不然就有你好怕的
or you'll know the meaning of fear
保安
Security
有个小小的问题
We got a small problem here
好无聊
So boring
腿太短
Short legs
早该知道的
We should've known better
我都快饿死了
I'm starving here
他买到吃的的可能性有多大
What are the chances he gets our food?
大概几乎没有
Slim to none, I'm guessing
在吗
Hello?
谁来帮我拿下这个
Could somebody help me with this?
25磅儿童热狗
全家桶
多加邪恶酱
And extra Evil sauce
太邪恶了
Wicked
好啊
Awesome
为小个子队长干热狗
A Weenie toast to Captain Pipsqueak
一二万岁
Pip pip hooray
好了  队长
Okay, Cap
拿了这袋蜗牛粑粑
take this bag of snail droppings
放到那边那个台阶上面
and leave it on that doorstep over there
这里是脚侠家
It's the house of the Foot
他是做好事的超级英雄
He's a superhero do-gooder
理应让我们狠狠搞他一手
who deserves our worst
上
Go
好
Yes
我往袋子里加了点特制海霸糊
I added a little of my own special Chum Mix to the bag
小个子队长  欢迎加入邪恶帮
Captain Pipsqueak, welcome to E.V.I.L.
全称是
which stands for
恶人皆为大废物
"Every Villain Is Lemons"
好耶
Yeah
那么小个子队长  接下来做什么
So Captain Pipsqueak, what's next?
跟我一起统治世界
Follow me to world domination
蟹堡王
蟹老板
Mr. Krabs
又怎么了  小子
What now, boy?
可震惊到我了
Shiver me's lumbers
快把秘密配方交出来  老螃蟹
You might as well give us the secret formula now, Krabs
我是邪恶帮的新主谋
I'm the new mastermind of E.V.I.L.
什么  你们几个阿宅要去漫展了
What, you nerds going to a comic convention?
衣服不错  痞老板
That is a nice costume, Plankton
叫我小个子队长
The name is Captain Pipsqueak to you
抓住他们
Get 'em
肮脏泡泡
Dirty Bubble?
我才刚洗好衣服
But I just did my laundry
小偷
Thieves
你的肮脏烂手别来碰我秘方
Keep yer filthy, rotten mitts offa me formular
好
Yes
这不是统治世界的秘方
This isn't the formula for world domination
是三明治的秘方
It's a recipe for a sandwich
这有什么用
How does that work?
那个  有了秘方
Well, with that
我就能让这个人
I can put this guy
停业
Outta business
为什么要这样
Why would we ever wanna do that?
蟹黄堡可好吃了
These Krabby Patties taste great
对
Yeah
还给你  老板
Here you go, boss
真对不起
Sorry about that
继续多做蟹黄堡
Keep up the good work
不敢相信这个唬烂小个子
I can't believe this lousy pipsqueak
浪费我们时间
Wasted our time
可真是个犯罪天才
Some criminal genius he is
是吗
Right?
还邪恶大智慧呢  净瞎说
"Massive evil intellect," my eye
我的哈瓦那辣酱啊
Holy habanero
痞老板注定要被困在瓶中了吗
Is Plankton forever doomed to be bound by a bottle?
要被关进玻璃里了吗
Grounded in glass?
不
No
要被裹进邪恶酱里了吗
Enveloped by extra Evil sauce
不准外带调料
No outside condiments
倒霉透了
Well, this stinks
海底飞机
编剧
分镜总监
翻译: 1440kHz
动画总监
指导总监
统筹
联合监制
监制
本字幕仅限学习交流
严禁用于商业用途
啊  多美好的早晨
Ah, what a beautiful morning
来看看邮件
Time to check the mail
知道谁在暗恋你了  章鱼哥
and see who loves you, Squidward
不知道能不能退给寄件人
I wonder if I can return to sender
早安  章鱼哥
Good morning, Squidward
我要回去睡觉了
Well, I'm going back to bed now
睡一辈子
Forever
你不开邮件吗
Aren't you gonna open your mail?
快给我
Gimme that
你们早都开完了
It looks like you already did
我赢奖了
I won something?
你获胜了
机票
座号2B
可我没参加比赛
But I didn't enter any contest
可以去免费旅游
It's an all-expenses-paid trip
看美丽的波拉波拉海滩
to see beautiful Bora Bora Bottom
我们替你参加的  而且只参加了六千次
We entered it for you, and only 6,000 times too
我  赢家
Me, a winner
去热带度假胜地
at a tropical resort
来看看
Let's see
获胜家庭将前往裤头村机场与
"The winning family will board
at Bikini Bottom Airport and the"--
等一下
Wait a minute
获胜家庭
"Winning family"?
我们是不是忘了说
Did we forget to mention
完蛋
Oh, no
不敢相信
I cannot believe
我让你们俩臭鱼烂虾骗进来了
I let you bottom-feeders talk me into this
为了你这样的朋友最起码也要这么做
It's the least we could do for a friend like you
我是说  为了你这样的爸
I mean, for a dad like you
老爸
Daddy
你们两个白痴
Will you morons--
我是说
I mean
小朋友  打住
children, please
下一位
Next
机票
各位旅客请注意
Attention, passengers
来见见海底航空大赛获胜者
Meet Underwater Air's big contest winner
章鱼哥和他的可爱一家人
Squidward Tentacles and his adorable family
这位宝爸快来
Come on, Dad
给你跟你家孩子拍张照
Let's get a picture of you and the kids
加到机上杂志里
for our in-flight magazine
好了  一家人
Okay, everybody
说  我爱我家
say, "I love my family"
我不想说
I'd rather not
快说
Say it
我爱我家
I love my family
你坐我位子上了  老爸
I think you're in my seat, Pop
我坐过道
And I'll take the aisle
老爸坐在中间
Daddy's in the middle
不行
Oh, no
这趟航班我绝对不要
I am not suffering a whole flight
夹在你们俩个呆头中间受苦
between you two barnacle brains
起码让我坐过道
At least give me the aisle
不好意思  先生
Excuse me, sir
你是否坐在指定的位置上
Are you in your assigned seat?
好的  各位旅客
Okay, everybody
请系好安全带
please fasten your seat belts
可以调节这个容易拉的带子
by adjusting this easy-to-pull strap
一定要往紧了系
Make sure it's nice and tight
保持座位直立
And keep your seat in the upright position
否则后果自负
Or else
好
Okay
看着不错
These look good
派大星  要不要换个位置
Hey, Patrick, wanna switch
让我看窗外风景
so I can look out the window?
好
Okay
不过要快
But hurry
各位旅客请注意
Attention all passengers
这里是
this is, uh
本次航班的机长
your captain speaking
请保持你们的
Please keep your, uh
安全带系牢
seat belts fastened
即将
as we, uh
升空
gain altitude
旅途愉快
Enjoy your flight
你们可以逛
You may now roam about the, uh
座舱了
cabin
听见没  章鱼哥
Hear that, Squidward?
可以解开安全带了
You can take your seat belt off now
等等
Wait
把我解开
Untie me
天啊  饲料袋
Oh, boy, a feed bag
不眠不休的十二小时后
能不能小点声
Keep it down, will ya?
我要睡觉
I'm tryin' to sleep
我梦见我在海里
I dreamed I was in the ocean
我得去尿尿
and now I gotta pee
需要帮忙吗
Can I help you with something?
我要上厕所
Yeah, I gotta use a bathroom
没礼貌
Rude
我先来的
I was here first
这位旅客  另一位空姐怎么了
Hey, buddy, what happened to the other flight attendant?
她在上卫生间
She's in the bathroom
看见没
See?
空姐会救我的
The flight attendants will save me
按呼叫按钮就行了
Just need to hit that call button
晚上好  先生先生
Good evening, Mr. Sir
要现磨咖啡吗
Fresh coffee?
什么
What?
派大星  真的空姐哪去了
Patrick, where are the real flight attendants?
她们上卫生间上了好一阵子
They've been in the bathroom for a while
应该是咖啡喝太多了
I think they had too much coffee
这瓶咖啡你要不要
Now how about that coffee?
我不要
No, I don't want--
哇  章鱼哥
Wow, Squidward
你也太爱咖啡了
you really like coffee
各位旅客
Folks
抱歉遇上了强烈水流
Sorry about that turbulence
派大星
Patrick
你当上空姐了
They made you a flight attendant?
你也想当吗
You wanna be one too?
想
Yeah
不好意思  先生
Our apologies, sir
帮你弄干
Let's get you dried off
自由了
I'm free
点心时间
Snack time
完蛋了
Oh, no
够了
That's it
我要找机长投诉
I am filing a complaint with the captain
把我推去驾驶舱
Roll me to the front of the plane
飞行员
你们旅途是否愉快
Are you enjoying your flight?
我不愉快
No, I am not
自打起飞  这俩就一直在闹事
These two have been nothing but trouble
since we took off
现在他们又在顶替空姐
And now they've replaced the flight attendants
他们对空姐怎么了
What did they do with them?
我只开了卫生间门  机长
I just opened the bathroom door, Captain
就像这样
Like this
没人开飞机了
There's no one flying the plane
要怎么办
What are we gonna do?
就快坠毁了
We're gonna crash
应该可以想办法开飞机
I guess I can figure this out
对  这又有什么难的
Yeah, how hard could it be?
章鱼哥  相信你的直觉
Squidward, trust your instincts
我觉得
I suppose, uh
章鱼哥你看  就快到了
Look, Squidward, we're almost there
只要让飞机着陆就行了
Now all you gotta do is land this thing
别把大家给害死了
And not kill everyone
章鱼哥  章鱼哥
Squidward, Squidward
波拉波拉海滩
耶  章鱼哥
Yay, Squidward
波拉波拉海滩
Bora Bora Bottom
各位旅客请注意
Attention, passengers
我是你们的新任机长
this is your new captain speaking
现已抵达美丽的波拉波拉海滩
We have arrived at beautiful Bora Bora Bottom
等一下
Wait a minute
飞机明明停好了啊
I thought I stopped this thing
章鱼哥你看
Squidward, look
原来一直飞机都是自动驾驶模式
It was on auto-pilot the whole time
自动驾驶     开
耶  章鱼哥
Yay, Squidward
你什么都没干
You did nothing
不要  不要
No, no
一定要下飞机  畅玩度假胜地
I need to get off this plane and enjoy the resort
这又何必呢
Now why would you wanna do that?
这趟旅游只能去看波拉波拉海滩
You won a trip to see Bora Bora Bottom
住是住不了的  笨蛋
not stay there, silly
要走了
And there it goes
造化就爱弄人
Life is funny, isn't it?
我是本次航班的空姐
This is your flight attendant speaking
目前正在遭遇逆风
Looks like we're experiencing some headwinds
预计前往裤头村的返程需要24小时
and the present estimate
for our return flight to Bikini Bottom is 24 hours
不
No